<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<dialogs>

    
    <dialog concept="x-ray structures and target-based drug discovery" scenario="scenario-donothing.xml" description="the vital role of x-ray data to target-based discovery" poke_message="How does information from the x-ray structure of a protein help the design of a molecule that will bind the same protein?">
    	
        <intro>
In week 1, we discussed target-based and phenotype-based drug discovery approaches.  Why is x-ray crystallography very helpful to target-based drug discovery?
        </intro>
    </dialog>
    <dialog concept="trends in structures of enzyme inhibitors" scenario="scenario-donothing.xml" description="similarities of competitive inhibitors of an enzyme" poke_message="Why do competitive inhibitors for a given enzyme have similar structures, but non-competitive inhibitors can be structurally very different?">
    	
        <intro>
All enzyme inhibitors block the catalytic action of an enzyme, but not all inhibitors act in the same way.  Two types of inhibitors are competitive and non-competitive inhibitors.  Competitive inhibitors for a specific enzyme tend to look similar.  Non-competitive inhibitors for a specific enzyme may have almost no similarities.  Why do competitive inhibitors for an enzyme tend to have closely related structures?
        </intro>
    </dialog>
    <dialog concept="partial agonists and antagonists" scenario="scenario-donothing.xml" description="similar activity of partial agonists and antagonists" poke_message="How does a weak partial agonist block potential receptor response in the same way as a competitive antagonist?">
    	
        <intro>
Competitive antagonists suppress a receptor’s response.  Drugs that are antagonists are often called blockers (e.g., beta blockers).  Interesting, weak partial agonists are sometimes mistaken as competitive antagonists early in a discovery program.  How can weak partial agonists have nearly the same effect on a receptor’s response as antagonists?
        </intro>
    </dialog>
                          
    <dialog concept="FINISH" scenario="scenario-donothing.xml" description="">
    	
        <intro>
And now we’re done. Thanks for joining us, have a great day! I will now continue the chat activity again starting from the first prompt for those who missed the initial prompts.
        </intro>
    </dialog>   
</dialogs>
